<resources>
    <string name="app_name">
        Coffee Info
    </string>
    <string name="esp">
        In its pure form, espresso is more popular in Europe than America, particularly in Italy.
        Though catching in America, derivatives and misconceptions are spreading like cream in coffee.
        For instance, many hold the misconception that espresso is a dark, bitter to burnt-flavored roast of coffee.
        In fact, espresso is not a roast at all; it is a method of preparing coffee. Espresso coffee is often blended from several roasts and varietals to
        form a bold - not bitter flavor. The finely ground coffee is tightly packed or tamped into a “portafilter”; high-pressure water is then forced through
        the grounds and extracted in small, concentrated amounts. Intensity is the key here.
    </string>

    <string name="capp">
         A ‘traditional morning heart starter’. Steamed foamed velvety milk poured over one shot (1) of coffee oil extract made from 12gm of freshly ground
        beans producing 38ml of essence.Finished by topping with foam and a sprinkle of chocolate powder. Served in a pre heated vitrified ceramic cup.
        A cappuccino usually exceeds the height of the cup, making the foam visible above the side of the cup.
        The foam on top of the cappuccino acts as an insulator and helps retain the heat of the liquid, allowing it to stay hotter longer."
    </string>

    <string name="amer">
An Americano is an espresso-based drink designed to resemble coffee brewed in a drip filter,
        considered popular in the United States of America.
        This drink consists of a single or double-shot of espresso combined with up to four or five ounces of hot water in a two-demitasse cup.
        It is important to note, that an Americano is created by adding the water to an already extracted espresso,
        not by extracting extra water through a single espresso puck.
        An Americano can be produced from lighter roasted coffees and roasts not generally associated with espresso, such as Ethiopian or Sumatran origins.
        While some state that the Americano was created in Europe to deride the perceived American taste for weaker coffees,
        it is more likely that it was developed in the United States city of Seattle.
        A well-made Americano retains the subtle aroma of espresso with a lighter body and less bitterness.
    </string>

    <string name="caffe">
        The term as used in English is a shortened form of the Italian caffè latte , caffelatte or caffellatte,
        which means "milk coffee". The word is also sometimes spelled latté or lattè in English with different kinds of accent marks,
        which can be a hyperforeignism or a deliberate attempt to indicate that the word is not pronounced according to the rules of English orthography.
        Caffè latte is a coffee-based drink made primarily from espresso and steamed milk. It consists of one-third espresso,
        two-thirds heated milk and about 1cm of foam. Depending on the skill of the barista, the foam can be poured in such a way to create a picture.
        Common pictures that appear in lattes are love hearts and ferns. Latte art is an interesting topic in itself.
    </string>
    <string name="lait">
        Café au lait is coffee with hot milk added. It differs from white coffee,which is coffee with cold milk or other whitener added.
        Café au lait is a French coffee drink. In Europe, "café au lait" stems from the same continental tradition as "caffè latte" in Italy,
        "café con leche" in Spain, "kawa biała" ("white coffee") in Poland, "Milchkaffee" in Germany, "Grosser Brauner" in Austria, "koffie verkeerd"
        in Netherlands, and "café com leite" in Portugal, simply "coffee with milk". In northern Europe, café au lait is the name most often used in coffee shops.
        It is a coffee beverage consisting strong or bold coffee (sometimes espresso) mixed with scalded milk in approximately a 1:1 ratio.
    </string>
    <string name="mocha">
        Caffè Mocha or café mocha, is an American invention and a variant of a caffe latte, inspired by the Turin coffee beverage Bicerin.
        The term "caffe mocha" is not used in Italy nor in France,where it is referred to as a "mocha latte". Like a caffe latte, it is typically one third
        espresso and two thirds steamed milk, but a portion of chocolate is added, typically in the form of sweet cocoa powder, although many varieties use
        chocolate syrup. Mochas can contain dark or milk chocolate.Like cappuccino, café mochas contain the well-known milk froth on top, although
        they are sometimes served with whipped cream instead. They are usually topped with a dusting of either cinnamon or cocoa powder.
        Marshmallows may also be ded on top for flavor and decoration.A variant is white café mocha, made with white chocolate instead of milk or dark.
        There are also variants ofthe drink that mix the two syrups; this mixture is referred to by several names, including black and white mocha, tan mocha,
        tuxedo mocha and zebra.
    </string>
    <string name="macho">
        Caffè macchiato is an espresso-based coffee beverage consisting mostly of coffee with a small amount of milk. Translating from the Italian phrase meaning
        marked coffee, this drink is made by "marking" a single shot of espresso with a few drops of frothed milk and served in a demitasse. Relative to other
        espresso-based drinks, a caffè macchiato is closer to a straight espresso, containing substantially less milk than a cappuccino . It can be used as an
        alternative to adding sugar to espresso, muting the bite of the espresso without adding sweetness.
    </string>
</resources>
